Are you still planning with MD files?
Maybe that's not the better output that
you can have. And what about HTML files?
That's what TK from Entropic wrote about
last week. He's planning everything with
HTMLs because it's prettier than MD
files. You can actually like draw some
chart and stuff to have better plans.
We're going to demo that workflow. So,
uh if you are intrigued, watch the
video.
Yes.
>> Yeah. Did you ever try it before the
live stream or like this week?
>> I wanted to try it but
>> yeah.
>> I said create a documentation and just
did MD by default.
>> Okay.
>> And then I asked for HTML and HTML was
just like still the MD
>> but only uh like H1 tag in front of it
instead of one hashtag.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Because Yeah. Macdonald
with MG file.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. So it didn't do what I wanted to
do. Yeah,
>> but let's try again together then. HTML
is the new markdown. I have stopped
writing markdown file for almost
everything and switch to use to generate
HTML for me. This is why Markdown has
become the dominant file format used by
agent to communicate with us. It's
simple port rich text capability and
it's easy for you to edit that. But as
agents have become more and more
powerful, I have felt that Macdon has
become a restricted former. I found it
difficult to read a Macdon file or more
than 100 of lines. You get your you get
your plan. You get the output of the
plan. It's a HTML file. We can I guess
you can compare you can even like have
different uh output of the plan or
exactly what you're doing right like
when you have three version of the onput
you can visualize whatever you are doing
directly into the plan that I I can see
that powerful for example if you want to
redesign a component you can have three
different version in a preview HTML
right the unreasonable effectiveness of
effectiveness of HTML uh 20
self-contained HTML files an agent
produce instead of a wall of Macdown.
Okay. So, three code approach. Yeah,
exactly. So, that's I can see why it's
powerful.
>> Yeah, you have more more options, more
possibilities
>> like that. That makes sense. Like Yeah,
I have some uh I have some different uh
different way of coding it and then I'm
ratedly that that's cool visual. Yeah,
no task. Yeah, that's cool. Illustration
illustrational. Okay. So you have empty
state of
uh of the plan timeline. Yeah, that's
cool. Open question. Do we all editing
or delete and repost? Okay.
Review annotate p request write up.
Yeah. Okay. That's cool. Okay. Okay.
Okay. That's that's pretty cool. Map
design. Yeah, that's lit front end and
stuff. That's that's interesting. And
that's the plan, right? This file is
supposed to be the plan at the output
plan that we we will have, right?
>> Yeah, but this is more like a brand
book.
>> Yeah, but that's also a plan. You can
choose and change like the colors and
stuff like that. And later in the
article, you can even like have to go to
change the plan directly like
interactively data ingestion. Why use
cloud cut to HTFI instead of cloud AI or
cloud design for example? One of the
biggest reasons is uh all the context
code can ingest. Oh, so you the size of
the context because you want to send
HTMLs. Really? Really?
>> They earn more money if they do.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, it's an
>> You're spending more tokens.
>> Yeah. And I'm really curious if we can
test for an um asking the AI agent to do
it in the in MD file and HTML file, make
it as optimized as possible and then
give him and ask him which one he
prefers, which one is most optimized
>> and what what is the most cheapest to
process.
>> We're going to try that right after.
>> Yes.
>> Is it less token efficient? While Macdon
often use fewer token, I found that the
added expressiveness of HTML and the
much higher likelihood of me reading it
means I get overall better output. Okay.
With the 1 million context with in OPUS
4.7, the increased token usage is not
really noticeable. Yeah. Because the
rest of the the of the model is so
expensive that if it's you don't see it,
>> but still this is a stupid answer.
>> Yeah.
>> Isn't it less token efficient? Yes or
no? And then you get a full [__]
answer, but he doesn't answer it.
>> Yeah. He says it doesn't matter. That's
that's the answer.
>> He answer it. He say, "Yeah, it's more
expensive."
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, when do you do when do you use
Markdown for now? I've honestly stopped
using Mark.
>> All the big IT guys who are really
smart. So many views with just the
notification of ask for HTML.
>> Yeah. So, let's do exactly the same
[__]
>> Yes.
You know what? We are going to uh do an
app to check if the uh the repository is
using the tan stack that has been uh
compromised.
>> Yes.
>> And hope it says no.
>> I want to build a micro app to check the
vulnerability of opensource uh project
that have been impacted by the latest
attack of the tanstack packages. Nice.
see the accent and stuff. It's perfect.
>> Almost stands you perfectly.
>> Yeah.
Uh all of the uh impacted package are
listed in that article.
Uh plan the app and I want the output of
the plan HTML file HTML artifact for the
plan. also added an MD so we have both
so we can compare
>> and also add the MD file so we can
compare uh the outputs and I want to
tell me how how many talk you use to
generate the plan in MD file and HTML
and the app uh will also generate HTML
report okay both plan artifact I created
4,000 for the plan MD and so yeah almost
double
>> yeah 50% expensive
>> uh HTML version use 63% more output
token due to the markup still signing.
Yeah, whatever. Open plan. Okay, cool.
So,
>> open it.
>> Yeah. Wow. So, that's the MD file. Uh,
that's quite long, but that's that's
readable. I mean,
>> yeah, but
I don't know. The the code editors I
use, they always have a second screen
beside it when I open an empty file, so
I can see code and preview.
Uh okay. So on cursor it's an extension
where you can preview the markdown
preview. Look.
>> Yeah. And then it's readable.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like Yeah. There is nothing
crazy here, right? Uh to uh
uh to to review. Anyway, so okay. And
now I'm going to open the mg uh HTML
file. Wow. It's the same [__] but
purple. Yeah, different colors.
>> Okay, that's cool. Completely.
>> It's like bootstrap styling over it in
dark mode.
>> Read both plan uh files and tell me
which one will is more consistent for
you and more useful
and cheaper to implement. I've read both
file. They contain identical content.
The same sh plan in two format.
>> Mhm. lines 200 for the MD file and
almost 600 570 for the plain HTML
estimate token three 3.8 6.2 to so
signal to nose high pure content low 200
line of CSS HTML B plate yeah
uh consistency table block and
unambiguous
that's interesting
uh plan MD is a clear winner for on all
three criteria h
recommendation use plan MD Yeah,
>> it works both, but HTML is just more
nice to look at and and more expensive
to use.
>> Yeah,
I mean that's all experimentation.
>> I mean we just wanted the plan, right?
It's just for as a output plan. So yeah,
for the general evaluation. Yeah, like
Okay. Okay. So
>> if you use it for internal planning,
they use the MD files. If you want to do
reporting and and use it for sharing
with people, you can do the HTML. That's
what I think.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah. Okay. So
like Yeah, it's it's like almost uh you
don't use either like uh just one, use
both basically.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Uh I think that's it.
>> Should we Yeah. Okay, that's it. That
was See, nice demo. Good job, Tim. So,
Mitchell, are you going to use HTML?
Now,
>> if I want to share something nice for
you, I'm going to use HTML, but as soon
as I want it to be optimized and use it
for planning internally, all all MD
files.
>> Yeah.
>> How about you?
>> I mean, again, I I I can see a use case
for components for sure. If I want to
redesign a component, I will ask to a
preview in HTML because that doesn't
like for a couple of percent of token
more like I would rather iterate on
content
uh on on the HTML with HTML files to
redesign something and I'm using code
for design and more like all of the rest
of the execution I use codeex anyway. I
don't I still don't use CH GPT 5.5 for
design because it's the taste of the
model is [__] So I will definitely use
code and the front end scale to do front
end stuff and delegate all of the
implementation the rest of the
implementation tox.
>> Perfect. Yeah. Nice. Okay. Awesome. We
>> that was it.
>> Yeah. We have a good demo if we have did
like a 26 minutes introduction.
>> But that that's that's talents, man.
That's talent.
>> Yes.
>> So, Mitchelle, thank you so much for
your time and everyone in the chat and
in the if you are watching the video
until the end, uh please subscribe,
like, share it with your friends because
we need it. Uh we are still
we missed some subscribers to 1 million
subscribers. So, it's time to it's time
to subscribe.
>> Yeah. Let them come in.
>> Yeah. Uh and that's it. Bye.
>> See you next week.